#### Contact

lesdeherde@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lesliedeherde-msn-rn-bc-cen-bb962ba4 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Information Technology Healthcare Hospitals

### Certifications

Six Sigma LEAN
Informatics Nursing
CEN

# Leslie Deherde MSN,RN-BC, CEN

Emergency Nurse Manager ASAP Credentialed Trainer Hope, New Jersey

### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Patient Safety, and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Project Management. Strong education professional graduated from Thomas Edison State College.

## Experience

Hackettstown Regional Medical Center Nurse Manager, Emergency Department September 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months) Hackettstown, New Jersey

Manager of a community emergency department. Improving workflows by improving efficiency, Chair of the ASAP Epic Optimization Work Group for Atlantic Health Systems, optimizing the current documentation to drive compliance with quality measures.

Atlantic Health System
Epic Credentialed Trainer, ASAP
October 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)
Livingston, NJ

Involved in curriculum development and class schedules for multiple roles. Directed training videos to use with Specialty Narrator training. Trained Emergency Department employees including providers in the ASAP application for a new implementation.

Provided at the elbow support during go-live at 5 facilities, including resolving tickets and identifying issues.

Atlantic Health RN Unit Educator May 2004 - Present (16 years 1 month) Morristown Memorial Hospital Informatics Nurse September 2015 - September 2018 (3 years 1 month) Morristown, NJ

Epic Readiness owner for a multiple hospital Health System managed systemizing policy and workflows. Liaison to other applications including clinical documentation, Grand central, Patient Access and radiology.

East Orange General Hospital - 300 Central Avenue Emergency Room RN May 1985 - October 1993 (8 years 6 months) East Orange, NJ

## Education

Thomas Edison State College

MSN with a speicality in Nursing Informatics, Master of Science

Nursing · (2008 - 2015)